



Baldoceda Alexandra

Graphic Designer Since **1995**

Hola!

Hi! I'm Ale Baldoceda from Lima, Perú. I'm 24 and i'm passionate about graphic design.

I really enjoy involving in different projects to find an excepcional visual solution creating brand experience with a significative impact.

I'm interested in social networks and the positive role that it plays in the society. Brand identity and editorial design..

Experience

Colegio Newton College - La Molina Marzo - Abril 2016 Photography

Agencia Noviembre - MirafloresDesigner Graphic
Comunnity Mannager

Rustica - Breña 2016 - 2017 Designer Graphic - Freelance

Salsa Agency - Miraflores 2018-2019 Designer Graphic

Education

C.E.Pq. María de la Providencia Primaria / 2002-2007

C.E.Pq. María de la Providencia Secundaria/ 2008-2012

Instituto de Publicidad , Diseño y Marketing / Leo Design Duración: 3 años Egresada - Diseño Gráfico Publicitario

4

Awards

Agency: Salsa

Brand: Huevos La Calera "Con Huevos al Cole"

- Festival de la Publicidad Independiente - Rosario 2018
- Premios Latam Digital Bogotá 2018
- WINA-World Independent Advertising Awards - Los Ángeles,Ca 2018

Software

Adobe Ilustrator

•••••

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe InDesign

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere